Youtube subtitles download by mo.dbxdb.com
* Subs by sonofdragons *
He is on his journey through time
and play the shitty games of yore.
Rather, he could be of a buffalo
his entire ear with Sprühstuhl befüll'n.
He would rather the rotting ass
a run over skunk licking and runterspül'n with beer.
A more furious gamer you have not heard before.
He's the Angry Nintendo Nerd.
He's the Angry Atari Sega Nerd.
He's the Angry Video Game Nerd.
Okay, the wait is finally over.
The review wants to see everyone.
Here it is: Superman ...
On the Commodore 64
That you thought surely, the Commodore 64 One of the best-selling home computer of the 80s.
The games were on floppies. Do you know the more that were still really wobbly?
We plug the fucker in there, turn on the bastard and play a little Superman.
This is the start screen. Without the instructions you were quite in a fix here.
You must then press Return LOAD "*", 8,1 and enter.
Then there is short black and a few seconds later "Superman is loaded."
At least you know then that you have it done properly.
Then you have but to wait until the shit part has loaded.
Do you remember, in the early CD-based consoles like the PlayStation
where you had to wait for whatever load times?
This is again of NEM completely different caliber.
This part needs it actually 2:07 minutes.
I admit it, I've measured.
Then the title screen comes with the music and you think to yourself "WOW!"
But what is it?
"Give the character from column 9, line 10 shows"?
Oh come on, I need so ne code table.
Yes, ne code table. Compare the stupid numbers and there you have it: it is the 5th
WHAT DO I NEED TO MAKE stuff like that?
So choose the difficulty level and before you know it, it must have been reloaded!
54 seconds this time, not necessarily long, but one seems like half an eternity.
Then you can get such a comic story and then ... you stupid fucking part!
Presumably one is two weeks later, after you finally can start playing times,
quite surprised that the video actually looks quite good and the controls are self-explanatory.
It just flies around and Ballert broken stuff.
You do not run around as Clark Kent, find underground tunnel or something a fuck.
So it's actually better than the Nintendo version.
But that has not much to say.
As if the shit last night was better than the shit from the day before.
The controller is fully Asspen.
But at least you can replace the against an Atari or Sega Mega Drive controller.
Is not that amazing?
The first level has a 3D perspective and in the second one protects a ship from Asteoroiden.
This one is more like a space shooter.
The third level is like a sidescroller, variety is thus available.
But this must be one of nervtötendsten level in the history of video games!
Each hit you will be thrown back!
Crap!
Damn!
Shit!
SHIT!
Sick of the dirt!
But wait, that's not what you want to see, I want to see THE here, right?
Oh come on, you really want me to play it?
Well, I do it only to please you. Because I really like to have you.
Take the merely not too serious!
Here we go! I turn it on!
First, you are greeted by a smiling cartoon fox.
"Titus"? What that?
The official title of the game is simply "Superman".
But since each game title on the N64 ended on 64, it is not surprising that it enjoys the same reputation.
The first thing that bothers me is this standard music ...
Why not the Superman theme? You know that. John Williams
The have the fewest games anyway!
Once the game starts you have to fly through rings.
I did not even get used to the control the time.
One would think that if the game has one starts a little room to fly around and look around.
But no, you have to fly through the rings!
And woe to you fucked up!
If you have more than, I think, missed three or so, no idea, sometimes two or four's.
I'm not quite sure, but in any case, if you miss a couple of rings you have to start from scratch.
And you try again and again until it works and on top of that there's still a time limit!
Since it is the very first level one would think that this is still a bit loose.
Forget it! The time is just enough so the whole hinzukriegen perfect.
It might look that I am feathering as a buffoon, but the controls are totally stupid.
You must be very precise to deal with the joystick, otherwise flying Superman sometimes just somewhere else entirely.
And if you want to fly a sharp turn to fly across the whole map.
You know the worth sure all better than me and it is hardly the mention of,
but this game is atrocious!
And you know what that is all-embarrassing?
The game is not even TEN years old!
Just how it is. One would think there were around 1999 already certain quality standards.
What? I firmly hang? How the hell can I get stuck? I am under the bridge!
It looks as if Superman jerk his Superschniedel.
Of course, you are under pressure when a game requires a one-time limit.
You can fly through any of these rings with peace or patience, you have to keep moving.
If you miss a ring one has to turn the dial and still to bring him,
so you have to expect no consequences unless you skip it and fetches the next.
But if you decide to turn around and get him, you have already wasted so much time,
So it is pretty much out of it the same if you just misses him.
You MUST continue to fly! If you start rumzueiern you no longer creates it within the time.
Watched? I have too much rumgeblödelt. So I can just as well give up and kill me.
Do you see as the building? I crash because now purely full pot.
Well, then it has nothing at all times brought!
You can not even commit suicide? Not at all!
It simply depends only in the air until the time runs out.
The only thing worse than an unspeakably verhunztes game is not even to have a choice to commit suicide.
What does that fidgeting? Can I beat up anyone in this Kackspiel?
I'll probably never find out, but why see these blows so disabled?
You want to piss me well! I hang already fixed again?
I'm not even in the sewing - looks like a lot of space! Look at the place!
How can I hang if there is sooo vieeel place?
15 seconds, and I've almost done.
Almost there! Oh shit, I missed tion ring. Oh come on! War I do not have a try?
Oh man, what's he doing now? Stretching exercises?
This is so pathetic. This game is not just bad, it is incredibly bad!
Oh, we should not fool ourselves, it's a bunch of steaming horse shit!
Almost there, less than ten seconds.
Come on, I can still just create so. Since the last ring!
Damn arschgefickter shit Hurenmösenfurz! I do not believe it! Because of the one ring!
Oh, that's Asspen, something of Asspen!
Oh, this time I'll get it! Only four seconds! Shit! YES!
NEEEEEEIN! That did not count!
So when I finally get the rings have left behind me, dive quickly to instructions and disappear.
What was there? Something to do with cars. You do not get time enough time to read.
Oh, it's already over? What I should have done that?
WHAT? I can not even try it again?
I HAVE AGAIN BY THE RINGS FLY SHIT!
I can not believe that I'm playing a Superman game where you do nothing but fly through rings!
At first I thought that would be the training mode to practice aiming.
Many games have that, eg Starfox on the Super Nintendo.
There's also nen training mode where you fly through rings.
But even then does not all get one, it's more about how many you get one after the other.
In the actual game you are flying through the area, ballert from enemies and avoid obstacles.
So what the fuck is this?
One should rather beat up nasty types
and do not ever put his flying skills with one of the most miserable controls prove!
There is even a practice mode.
And just out of pure curiosity I once tried it to see what it is and three guesses.
Fly through rings, jup. What else?
So I am arrived back at the next part.
The message remains just a second on the screen.
And then you have six seconds for whatever.
Fuck! Back at the rings back.
If I had two consecutive trials, perhaps I would sometimes figure out what I should do.
But instead, I am so surprised that I've managed to
than that I can respond to something within six seconds, without being able to read what I should do.
And I really do this to me? Is that a Superman game
in which you can fly only by rings?
What better is that not invaded?
That would be like a Batman game, in which he plays Hüpfekästchen.
Okay, it's time for the six-second auto-level.
Way! Go away since!
All right, I got the car. And now?
Oh, the clock has to eleven seconds reset. All well and good, but what do I do with the car?
There's another car, I can stop it?
Oh, that sucks. The. Is. Shit.
Basically, you have to stop the car before they drive people to the ground.
But guess what comes next?
Even more rings!
And then you have to pick up a patrol car and contribute to the goal.
I urge here slow on a pattern.
Fly through rings, pick up cars, drag back by rings and more cars.
So I come to the finish and three guesses what comes next.
Seriously, guess what comes next.
Even more rings. Right.
What is this game? Is that something like a psychological test?
I've had enough of it at any rate, more of it I did not pack.
This game qualifies as not even shit.
This is more of a shit shit Kackbatzens.
This is so unspeakably and so shockingly bad!
It is abhorrent and repugnant racking a brain!
There is one big pile of shit and does not belong on this planet!
Someone has to bother about! This looks like a job for the fucking nerd!  Subtitles End: mo.dbxdb.com