Youtube subtitles download by mo.dbxdb.com
The Terminator 2 movie right candidate for the "best resume ever made" address
and "Best Action and Sci-Fi Film 'title as well.
Wherever you look, it's a masterpiece.
Naturally, the video games they wanted to ride the success
therefore, have appeared on the market.
It is likely that what most of us know, the arcade version of Midway onwards.
We can now re-ported Sega Genesis and Super Nintendo.
The gameplay does not need a lot of sense:
just move the cursor on the screen, and shoot anything that moves.
Except the Companions of the way they are because they are dirty.
Well, hear! I did not know that Gold terminators are doing.
Defeating the Boss mindless butchers ground. More bullets to beleeresztened,
than you can imagine. Just shoot, shoot and shoot.
The Genesis version is similar to ROB the robot! (For an additional NES)
Essentially the same game, but with minor changes.
And some of the sound effects are right.
The Super Nintendo version, and if the soldiers is shot, I shout: No!
Which is pretty lame.
But the Genesis version, just yell.
Tremendous progress ...
Sticking out from under the horse's feet some animation. Look at the barrel! The flames did not move.
Unlike the Super Nintendo's version, collect items from the first track.
So ... um ... small refrigerator are looking for things. It seems that you never run out!
Yet many current half power for such a small box?
The worst part is when you have to protect John Connor.
All that happens is always to kill, and you lose.
A meaningless game, but in its day it was a real standard.
The home consoles wanted to take advantage of it.
The Super Scope pal and Sega Menacer per year.
But where is really worth playing, that was the game room.
Moreover, even for GameBoy also átportolták.
Now that's pathetic!
Now comes the Terminator 2 NES.
Everything begins with the death of small rainbow ...
I swear, I do not want to be prejudiced, but a lot of freakin crap LJN game released!
All Terminator 2 game console in seeing them, even the arcade transcripts as well.
"The LJN proudly presents". So to sum I pay!
Of course this is a different kind of gameplay it offers compared to the arcade version.
The first track. You're the Terminator, and a truck Stopped hitting people.
Pointless speculation is the whole key presses, in addition eltalnod need them often,
to die.
I just need to run to from them.
But you can not. Do you know why? Because the quest to hit everyone out on the track.
The sound effects are totally sucking. Only:
There is no difference between having just hit the air, or if you hit someone.
You could not have two distinct sound effects to create?
God, it lasts for eternity!
If among you, shoot it. But even if all of them on one page cheat,
sit together and you can often get hit.
This is only the first part of the game, and you've got it I'm sick of fucking!
Then you go to the pub as the first scenes of the film.
Again, all you need to shock him, but constantly pouring from the bar.
Yet how many are there?
Then you get to the main enemy. Just who is this guy?
Higher you while you're in the Terminator?
Arnold "Fucking" Schwarzenegger?
But it is not the size of the point, is not it?
Look, I died. Canned feet from a Terminator, a machine with his bare hands!
Well this is odabasz.
If you crouch down, you can not hit. Gyepálhatom So as long as I want.
But it can last forever, and do not think that is damaged by shocks.
So why put a character in the game who behaves as if it gets damaged,
While you seem to be fine?
It seems like you get out of him ...
It can kill, but with a little patience is necessary.
The second track. This is the only track where you sit on the bike.
Something you should know: you need to shoot the gate, otherwise it will end collision.
Once shot, you still have, if not completely in the middle of lime.
Reminds me of Bart Vs. from the World, the Great Wall of China when Bart roams change.
I hated that shit!
But the most annoying thing in the truck! From the bottom of the screen will be in it, at heart!
Yet what is it, a magnet on the front?
First of all, when I played, fart was not what I should do.
I was thinking that we should speed up, but I could not find a way to succeed.
Finally I realized that I can shoot back. All you have to do is you shoot the truck,
as if ... then rolled forward. But to shoot the truck, and the ride is quite annoying to watch.
Then save John Connor, and you must swear not to kill anyone.
So, come the third track where the hospital trying to save Sarah.
It should not to shoot anyone unless lábonlövöd.
It is quite clear, but damn stupid comes out to be always squat.
I mean, this is the first side-scrolling field, where a gun,
and you can not kill anyone.
The fourth track. The Cyberdine in or
and the mission is to fly in the air the place up.
You pace back up to gyüjtögess bombs, which looks like ...
I do not know. A headless chicken that just takes a dead rat?
Why not? Do not you see?
I do not know.
I work up the bombs, and lays them some crap store or something.
And I think that's all, right?
Is not it! Who should consider the bombs and reassemble them at the place specified.
Okay, well what's the point of this? Why could not only collect the bombs
and eat your position where you? I can only imagine what they thought:
"Gonna put the bomb into the 'lookin' guy."
Okay, and then what?
"Why do not you take out back and put down somewhere else?"
Like dog new tricks! "Go to Ager, get, get back!" Little fuckers ...
The fifth track nightmare.
Wherever you go, mobile platforms have to jump.
The pontosságodnak should be better than perfect, or you're dead.
Fuck!
It is almost impossible!
Eljátszatja you the idea that comes down the chain. But no!
It's a big jump, amekkorát possible. But the platform does not stay down for long enough.
We're just a microsecond is to act! In addition there is a ball of fire!
Leghúzósabb snapped this one life.
Another jump like a glitch or something. Oh come on! It really killed?
The pipe arrived, not the lava.
If you kill the tube arrival, then why not look like it is lava?
And with what's going on here? That's a platform?
So what the fuck looks like a platform? Here then are in serious trouble ...
Finally duel T-1000. The bare your hands.
Unless you left your ammo from Cyberdine,
because there is no ammunition in the whole track! Not one ounce!
So if you have no ammo, just rely on your hand.
At least it would be a place where felpakolhatsz ammo!
Because it is the Last Battle! If you look at a game in the Castlevania-series
before you fight Dracula, you can spend a certain place again.
It is true that a secret, but it's there. In addition, there are guns in the hallway.
But here you do not get my ass either!
After the T-1000 in the lava pushed him win.
Then check out the last spots. It seems that every key scene
have been in the game, which is commendable, but being left out of the Terminator theme song
still amaze.
For now the Terminator 2 on GameBoy!
By portable console not expect a lot in graphics,
but resolved quite nicely. John Connor will shape the future, who just last Skynet.
The first track seems simple, until you reach the end of the lézersorompót.
Of course, you leave to the left to find out what you should do.
Then you realize that these towers kill the task.
After you blew them all, there is still a barrier.
In fact, it should be firing them from highest to lowest!
What a bunch of random crap!
The second track of Skynet in you, which is pretty obvious.
But these bombs on the ground well fuck him up!
I can not shoot them, and I can not jump over them.
Oh yeah. Do you know of three games without a life and Resume?
So here there is only one life! Once you die, the game is over.
I think that végigvidd the game so that you do not die, just crazy!
At the end of the second track to be the Terminator program it is.
Okay ... well, so did John Connor?
I never think that the history of this part of the play is written.
In essence, the wires should be tied to the circuit to work.
But there is a time limit! And you can always go down, when you start to figure out what to do.
You can not pause the game, it goes blank.
Here there are at least two options. But if you fuck up twice, then I've failed.
In the last game. Thank fucking God. Terminator 2 on the Super Nintendo.
And includes the Terminator headline?
No. Of course not.
Just a remastered version of ... crap
How many would do so Terminator game that was removed from the headlines?
The only thing that was in it, the Sega CD version.
If you look at the demo, you will see as a naked Arnold goes to the bar,
sensors and show the style of Austin Powers!
Now that's funny!
If you press START, you can skip the whole thing.
Then you have to dress and hang around together and back to hitting people.
I can only say: Oh, my God!
The management is very bad!
It is very hard, and you can not beat anybody if you're too close to them.
But watch the jump!
Yet what is good? Like some kind of disability, or as if an invisible rope pulling.
The bitch sky, now that's damn odabasz! Note that push:
God ...
I do not see the point. You can not make a joke esre something so random!
A very hard of someone who is the Terminator, they did a complete joke.
Well, that's a joke!
I did not do it because it's funny, but it is very slow walk.
The only way to move faster when jumping like an idiot!
Unlike the Nes version is not the one mission that leüss everyone.
You'll never run out. What a joke is when someone pretend:
"Hey, try it! Kill the guys! "It's definitely going to sit there forever!
The mission is to find a pistol and a rifle.
But that's not enough, you have to find John Connor's phone number.
But it's still not enough, because "objects in its future" must be collected!
I do not know what these things. But small coolers, first aid and similar crates.
I do not remember them from the movie, so why should such a force in the game?
If you have never played the game before, I'd think
If you find these objects, you also were collected.
But no! Them to be kept as a gun and shoot them.
Look at the briefing! He says: "Collect objects in Future"
So when I think of the collection means that you have to shoot the shit out of them
I can not write there is more to 'Destroy objects in its future? "
Which was not very fun, is that although the pieces explode for no reason.
Even the waitress attacked you!
All human beings turn off the game will be finished before the first pitch.
I go the whole hog to succeed, then I got this:
The small engine - if you believe, if you do not - you're in!
Can not be distinguished from the others. When I gave first-time,
died soon before he was figuring a chance to know what to do.
Oh and by the way: a Life.
Yeah Die once, and it's all over.
It clung to the formulation, is not it?
Play through the game in one breath! It's inconceivable.
Man, collided with the truck engine. And the truck exploded!
I must say, I still do not know how to control it.
The biggest problem is that I do not know how to turn around.
Somehow, they'd have to hold the D-pad, and the Ypszilont,
but just could not get the hang of. I can say without hesitation:
This is without a doubt the worst conductor part I've ever played.
Roger Rabbit was bad, Dick Tracy terrible.
Then I thought this was the worst.
But after playing with ...
this takes the cake!
I could only get so far, and that's Terminator game you have to play with.
Well, the worst with this prize won.
Of all the Terminator games are the worst!
Based on the criteria, here are the limits of the NES, Super NES and abilities.
Did you ever think that the Super NES version will be even worse?
In addition, this is the sequel! So there's no excuse for being worse.
Do yourself a favor and never-never play this game!
Because "there is no fate, but if you can finish the work." (The first sentence legendary film)
Choose the good fate and defeat this Fost hat!
Good-bye, baby ...
The caption was: Majin_Zed   Subtitles End: mo.dbxdb.com