Youtube subtitles download by mo.dbxdb.com
The present Gametrailers.com
the production of Cinemassacre.com
Screwattack.com the assistance of
Illustrations by Mike Matei
Written, directed, and edited by James Rolfe
IDENTIFICATION OF GAMES
Target locked
System: NES Edition in the U.S.: 1992 Developer: Mindscape
Possible responses: It sucks! No way! Oh no! What a piece of dog shit! Go to hell!
What a piece of dog shit!
Make games in the first Terminator movie? What an opportunity!
The film was a film-noir-like, was in action, science fiction, time travel, and it is well kneaded.
But the game is like macskahúgyot, horse shit and disznóhányást been kneaded together!
Yeah! This is a blender that you do not want to.
So if this game from them, will surely give you a stroke.
But do not worry! Because now is the time to lay the demons!
Because the battle for the past will take place in the present!
Here and now!
Man, it's too dark. I'd rather just start the game!
As you notice, the Terminator or not.
Kyle Reese or in the future, which will probably be the best idea.
But look at the gafikát! So I call this 8-bit vomit ...
Together, jumping back half missing bricks, pipes and projections.
Yet what is it? Super Mario Brothers?
The background is just gray bricks random mush.
Pretty depressing to look at.
Maybe I wrong?
The NES would do would not last enough to color?
The upper display is quite monochromatic, only black, white and green.
Look at the vitality of the strip!
The black shows the ténlyeges guilds, while green shows sold out in hand,
which is kind of confusing, because if you look at it,
I'm not sure, but I feel that the other way around.
The music is unacceptable. Listen!
Still, what would you call this?
It's only a five-second melody, which is repeated continuously
Sound effects are barely.
Pretty bad effect on the listener.
If your ears hányhatnának, you can do anything.
Now I want to talk to the management.
Dear God, well fucked up.
If you want to jump, first you get into the squatting posture
Probably the most late jump I've ever met.
The gun is even worse!
If you press A, and then you get into the squat position.
We call this "weapon mode".
If this "weapon mode" or the shot will be launched with the D-pad and célozhatsz.
Well, let me summarize:
You can not shoot when you stand, you can not shoot when you squat - as do otherwise - and if you can not shoot jump!
This is in contrast to all the usual stuff that works side-scrolling games, lövölzdözős.
The game designers have ever played Contra with?
Can you imagine how much that it causes problems that you can not shoot while jumping?
However, the biggest problem is that there is no possibility to continue.
If you die three times, the game character from the start.
It's that simple!
You better get used to the first scenario,
because often you'll see a whore!
The other big problem is that if you want to jump onto something
Ates then on it!
This inspriráló a very bad joke, legendarily bad game design.
Almost as bad as the Wizard of Oz.
Fucked up the injury.
If you want to shoot something, the bullet passes through it until you're perfectly correct.
This game is like a frustrated child who must leave to win!
To get rid of these automatic lövegektől,
it is best to use grenades.
But grenades only find the first parts of the channel.
Then, when you run out, fucked up!
At this point two guns at the same time have to handle.
Only some of them kill a separation,
therefore, the second to hit for sure you're going to get!
No matter how far you get, you still do not have the possibility to continue.
To my knowledge, there is no code, it does not even GameGenie to. Nothing!
The only way to végigvidd is not to fuck it!
As outrageous
However, 50,000 points, you get an extra life
Fair enough, so I'll stay here, and while I shoot this prick until it happens.
The enemies respawn, so it's not a challenge to stay in one place
and collecting goods points.
The only downside is that for a very long time to do it.
Finally, Extra Life.
From now on I will be very careful, because I do not want my work to go to waste so far.
Here's the fucking slime, you just do not pay attention ...
Awww, my God!
The only hope is if you spend many hours extra life by collecting as possible.
Quickly you can lose them, but you need at least to get new ones.
You who have enough patience for this?
No emulátorokról and job-saving we are talking about.
I'm talking about reality, when you sit in front of your TV, and holding down the A button.
Sounds good, does not it? But check this out! I have an idea!
Get a wrench or something, tighten down the A button
There you go!
Just sit back and do nothing fucking!
"I'll be back!"
Look at that! My life is already 6.
Now I go to bed, then come back and everything will be maximum.
Right, what was a good idea? But wait. I have a better idea!
There could be some fucking Resume!
Wrench to make the controller ... I want to do it all your life?
It's pointless. But to do this, man.
All right! I'm back! Fresh and fresh and,
ready to continue to play the terminator, and the extra life with.
Each of the six ...
Six?
Only six?
Okay I'll be honest.
Only one figure, I did not expect more than nine.
But why such a random number, like six?
This means having something fucked up masochistic
so programmed, and while this decision was made by:
"Let's see. We do not make more than six, because many will be. " Fucking asshole!
The only thing I can think of for now,
to die five times and start over again.
Then, suddenly, or a flatbed car, fireballs rain on you.
Only very little you can control the car, so the only thing you'll ever do
to die, you die, you die.
You can not hit because the projectile is scattered everywhere.
Eventually outpace the fucking machine.
But start immediately after you shoot a tank-metal monster simplicity.
At this point, just get inside the balls.
The only thing to do is hit, then again, again and again.
This part of the game again with a death trap.
Do you see what happened? Extra életeimmel?
They're gone!
And, unfortunately, are no longer adversaries.
So now it is hopeless me to get them again.
If you die, the game is over.
But here's the most annoying thing I've ever seen.
The spears no rhythm, just randomly show up.
So I must be lucky!
Look at those projections! They could be even smaller?
To think how hard it had been to finish touching
then try to imagine how crazy that is exactly halfway arrive
a place that is narrower than the character itself!
If you arrive on your foot, it does not matter. Must arrive at the empty space that is between your legs.
Fuck!
Okay, life is zero, so there is still a chance.
Skip ...
Fuck!
Fucking small! Fucking small!
"I was devastated!"
I can not believe that they were able to issue such a big shit NES
Moreover, in 1992.
1992nd Demeberében.
Well, it has been released for the Super Nintendo.
While we're here, let's look at the 16-bit version!
Thank goodness it's not the same game improved graphics.
This is completely different
However, I'm thinking that was used in the opening screen of the movie
but not the music. The music is the final confrontation.
It's like the Star Wars overture to use, but other music.
So you can not find one of these games, the Terminator-Original Song.
Once again, Kyle Reese or you're not in the sewers, but on the battlefield or
as seen in the movie visszaelékezésekben.
So we headed in the right direction!
The firing is much better. In this case, you normally shoot,
instead should squat.
Even the ladders can shoot too, which is pretty cool.
But what sucks, is that you can not shoot straight up or toward the ground.
There is no more perfect example of the Contra-Series takes.
Can shoot every fucking direction and challenging games to date.
But here fennakadsz those foes, you just find a grenade.
If you run out of grenades, fucked!
If you want to do a game in which you can not shoot toward the ground,
then do not do it any enemies that are in the fucking ground!
The graphics in the foreground are always in the way.
How fair is that you can barely see the enemy?
Otherwise, what the fuck are they? Decepticon-ballers? (The evil Decepticons in the Transformers-franchisee)
Look, I hit my head, and died.
It is quite surprising, but the game is quite difficult.
Now I can imagine what you had to kereszülmenni Reesenek Kyle and Johnny C's.
Keep running to a deserted area where machines are around, throwing grenades and shooting at you from left and right.
Crap shoot at you from the sky, the earth shit, shit everywhere!
You're going to be destroyed! Those films were not realistic.
There is no way to survive.
But the part-time occupancy vehicles, that's fine.
Look at the balls! No recurring schedule, and it's like a different player to control.
Time to react before it will appear on the terminator, and shoot at you.
It is quite difficult to transcend slowly, if your character can only run.
The only strategy is to crouch and move along
But even then, - it is still getting hit - half the time.
Not as often as you find it so far, but enough to die.
And just get him alive. If you run out of - you guessed it already ...
Proceed no. But it's okay because I did not finish the first level.
Do not seem difficult. But good heavens! It just goes on and on and on!
Five life and healing packages could not get on.
I got the car for a turn, which still belongs to the first scenario,
but this is worse than the NES diversified car parts!
I can shoot in three directions, which means that you can not hit this thing, if it does not come irányaidba.
And there's nothing there, which defend yourself.
You can not move around and get results from these explosive bowling ball from.
Finally disappears, and you can run out again.
After such a big sprint already think that the thing was probably the main enemy.
No, do not be naive!
Just keep doing the shitty ending marathon
which crap shoot, shoot at you and shit!
Finally, you arrive at the main enemy.
Large enough to be Boss, and so long as it did to get here
I can say that he is the Boss.
Die! Die! Okay, got it.
But now ..
What is it?
Now you fucking kidding me?
(That's the part that you think is impossible to translate into Hungarian ...)
That it is not over yet?
Yet how long can the first track? Unless the whole game is not like that ...
I can not fucking believe it!
Finally, I died like everyone else.
The end of the game, the first track is infinite, can not be transferred, and the story is that it is impossible to play.
Very quick peek at the Terminator Sega CD.
I've spoken a few words about the Sega CD in my video,
but now as I look at this huge improvement over the previous games.
There are some annoying things.
As in previous games, here are some directions which you can not shoot,
This makes it quite difficult to find an angle in which you hit the enemies.
I do not know why, but it seems that only the Contra has managed to achieve that.
Sometimes it is quite confusing to figure out which way to go.
And then there are the bushings from the film unwatchable, which is characteristic of the Sega CD.
In dreams would have thought that one day we can look better quality videos on the Internet!
But you can skip these vias, otherwise the game is a side-scrolling pretty good stuff.
And also includes the Terminator theme.
In addition, lots of great music!
God, this is fucking great!
Just a little bit better in the NES version, do not you think?
Well, from now things will only get better.
The second movie was better than the first, so I can expect from this game.
I believe that light waiting at the end of the tunnel. Survive the storm,
and there will be a rainbow after the storm.
A heart ..?
Oh, no!
Continued ...
The caption was: Majin_Zed (agyas91@freemail.hu)  Subtitles End: mo.dbxdb.com